newbirth.org 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy - New Birth Missionary Baptist Church-Lithonia, GA

**Purpose**

Thank you for visiting Newbirth.org, a site presented to you by New Birth Missionary Baptist Church. (“Newbirth”). New Birth Missionary Baptist Church (“New Birth”) recognizes that an individual’s privacy is very important to them and that they have a right to control their personal information. New Birth acknowledges that when an individual provides personal information about themselves to another party it is an act of trust. In response, New Birth takes the process of upholding an individual’s privacy very seriously. Unless an individual gives New Birth explicit consent to act otherwise, the following policy will govern how New Birth handles an individual’s personal information and safeguards their privacy.

**  
Scope**

The principles contained in this privacy document apply to all personal information collected or submitted to New Birth.

**  
Information Collected**

New Birth collects two different types of information. One type is voluntary information, which you provide, such as registration information for events, membership information, or shipping and billing information. The other type of information New Birth collects is user information provided by your computer each time you visit this site, such as IP address and browser. The information that New Birth collects helps us to provide information and service to you. We may combine information from other sources with the information that we collect.

**  
Use of Information**

Any information that you provide to New Birth or that is obtained through this website may be used for church purposes. New Birth will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to commercial entities. New Birth will not disclose your name, address, e-mail address or phone number without your express consent, unless disclosure is necessary to comply with laws or relevant legal proceedings.

New Birth may offer services to you such as chat streams, message boards, Facebook, twitter, or other similar forums. Please be aware that any information you divulge in these arenas is deemed public information and is not protected.

**  
Cookies**

Cookies are information that a website transfers to an individual’s PC for record-keeping purposes (e.g., if you are a USA Today Interactive user, a cookie on your PC allows you to go directly to the USA Today instead of having to give your user name and password each time). Cookies can save your preferences when you are at a site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and most major websites use them.

New Birth may use cookies to help us see which areas of our website are more popular, which are not, how they are being used so that we can improve and update our website to more accurately meet the needs of our users. At some point in the future, if New Birth decides to offer personalized services to its users, we will use cookies to make that personalization and customization of the New Birth website possible.

Most browsers (Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome) are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to either refuse all cookies or to notify you when you are receiving a cookie and allow you to decide whether or not to accept it.

We do not use cookies to obtain any personal information about you before or after you leave the New Birth sites.

**  
Links to Third Party Websites**

As a courtesy, New Birth may provide links to other sites that are neither owned nor controlled by New Birth. Some of these sites may use the New Birth logo. These third party sites, however, are NOT subject to or bound by the New Birth Privacy Policy. Such third party sites may or may not have their own privacy policies and may or may not collect personal information from you or place cookies on your browser. New Birth is not responsible for the privacy policies or any information collection practices of these sites or any damages resulting therefrom.

**  
Security**

The security of the information that you provide to us is very important to us. Consequently, we have taken several measures to protect your information. All transactions involving sensitive information, such as your credit/debit card number and expiration date, are conducted using a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection. This connection provides increased security to the information as it is transmitted to our website. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant its security.

**  
Changes to Our Policy**

New Birth reserves the right to change, amend, or restate this policy. Your continued use of this website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

**  
Your Consent**

By using New Birth’s website, you are giving us your express consent to use all the information that we collect about you in the manner described in this policy. This includes the release of such information to third parties as described above.

**  
Questions or Concerns**

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact our legal department at takingauthoirty@newbirth.org
